Contact

https:// gustavomarcelonunez.github.io/ portfolio/

gnunez@ing.unp.edu.ar

www.linkedin.com/in/gustavomarcelonunez

github.com/gustavomarcelonunez

github.com/gustavonunezlab

git.fi.mdn.unp.edu.ar/gustavonunez

Languages

English (Professional Working) Spanish (Native or Bilingual)

Certifications

Generative AI Fundamentals
Introduction to Responsible AI
Introduction to Generative AI
Introduction to Large Language Models

Publications

Mapyzer: una herramienta de carga y visualización de datos espaciotemporales

Visual Analytics for Linked Open Data in Marine Sciences

Análisis Visual para Datos Abiertos Enlazados vinculados a las Ciencias de Mar

Extracción y Explotación de Conocimiento para la Gestión en Línea de Datos en Ciencias del Mar

Integrating Oceanographic Sensor Data Using SSN/SOSA Ontology

Gustavo Marcelo Nuñez

Software Developer

Puerto Madryn, Argentina

Extract

University Programmer Analyst. Advanced student pursuing a Bachelor's degree in Computer Science, passionate about software development and Artificial Intelligence.

Since 2019, I have been serving as a student tutor at the Faculty of Engineering at the National University of Patagonia San Juan Bosco. Starting from 2020, I have also been working as a software developer.

I have had the opportunity to participate in research projects in collaboration with CESIMAR-CONICET, LINVI-UNPSJB, GILIA-UNCOMA, CIT-GSJ, and distinguished university professors from UNPSJB.

Currently, I am engaged in the visualization of Linked Data (LD) and knowledge graphs, involving processes of RDF data standardization and the use of ontologies.

Experience

CyberArg systems

Full Stack Developer march 2023 – Present

Puerto Madryn, Chubut, Argentina

National University of Patagonia San Juan Bosco. (UNPSJB)

Asistant - Mathematical Analysis

august 2021 - Present

Puerto Madryn, Chubut, Argentina

Second Assistant with part-time dedication in Mathematical Analysis, a first-year subject in the Bachelor's degree in Computer Science program.

Tutor

april 2019 - Present

Puerto Madryn, Chubut, Argentina

Active member of the Tutoring System at the Faculty of Engineering of the National University of Patagonia San Juan Bosco. Providing support and assistance to incoming students regarding university life matters.

Asistant – Computer Laboratory

april 2021 - february de 2023

Puerto Madryn, Chubut, Argentina

Student Assistant in the Computer Laboratory at the National University of Patagonia San Juan Bosco.

Software Developer

september 2020 - october 2021

Puerto Madryn, Chubut, Argentina

Development of a system for visualizing space-time data in urban environments, as part of an agreement between the National University of Patagonia San Juan Bosco and CONICET CENPAT. The project has been approved and presented at the CACIC 2021 School of Informatics.

Professor

september 2019 - december 2019

Puerto Madryn, Chubut, Argentina

Professor of Mobile Technologies and Computer Science for senior citizens

Professor

september 2019 - december 2019

Puerto Madryn, Chubut, Argentina

Computer Science Instructor for senior citizens.

Fundacion de Altos Estudios en Ciencias Comerciales

Professor

may 2022 - july 2022

Puerto Madryn, Chubut, Argentina

Professor of Applied Computer Science in the field of Business Sciences.

Chesca S.A.

Web Developer

september 2021 - january 2022

Puerto Madryn, Chubut, Argentina

Development of websites, primarily using WordPress. PHP module development.

Education

National University of Patagonia San Juan Bosco (UNPSJB)

Bachelor's Degree in Computer Science, Computer Science · (2018)

National University of Patagonia San Juan Bosco (UNPSJB)

University Programmer Analyst, Computer Programming (February 2018 - May 2021)